(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)You're an actress.
(Sheldon:)I need you to teach me.
(Penny:)You want an acting lesson?
(Sheldon:)Perhaps two. I'd like
to master the craft.
(Penny:)Okay, where
is this coming from?
(Sheldon:)It has been suggested to
me that acting techniques
(Sheldon:)could improve my
lecturing, at which,
(Sheldon:)if certain tweets and
blogs are to be believed,
I "suck the big one."
(Penny:)Yeah, I saw those.
They were funny.
(Penny:)I printed a few out
and put 'em on my fridge.
(Sheldon:)So, when could we start?
(Penny:)Okay, just to be clear.
(Penny:)You are asking me for help
because I know something
(Penny:)that the brilliant
Dr. Sheldon Cooper doesn't.
(Sheldon:)I suppose that's one
way to look at it.
(Penny:)I think it's the only
(Sheldon:)Are you going to
help me or not?
(Penny:)Probably. I'm just
enjoying the foreplay.
(Penny:)Does this mean you are done
mocking my acting career?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm sorry, I thought
making the transition
(Sheldon:)from actor to acting teacher
(Sheldon:)was the signal
that one's career
(Sheldon:)had reached the
end of the road.